socialmediatrafficblueprint.com 2018-08-16

# 

> **VIDEO MARKETING QUEEN PRIVACY POLICY**
> 
> This privacy policy sets out how Video Marketing Queen Inc. is committed to protecting the privacy and security of its online visitors. We want you to know how we use and protect any information that you give videomarketingqueen.com when you use this website.
> 
> Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website; you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Please note that your use of this website is also subject to the [Terms of Service](http://www.socialmediatrafficblueprint.com/tos.html) (of which this privacy policy is a part) also posted on this website.
> 
> Videomarketingqueen.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are comfortable with any changes. This policy is effective from October 15, 2008.
> 
>   
>  **WHAT WE COLLECT**  
>  We may collect the following information:  
>  • Name  
>  • Contact information including email address  
>  • Other information such as preferences and interests
> 
> **  
> WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER**  
>  We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with better service, and in particular for the following reasons:  
>  • To maintain accurate, up-to-date internal record keeping   
>  • To improve our products and services  
>  • To periodically send promotional email to the email address you provided about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting or of benefit   
>  • To contact you occasionally for the purpose of market research   
>  • To customize the website to reflect your interests 
> 
> **HOW WE USE COOKIES**  
>  A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 
> 
> We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages on our site are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes, after which the data is removed from the system. 
> 
> Overall, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not, cookies help us provide you with a better website. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 
> 
> You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
> 
>   
>  **CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**  
>  Videomarketingqueen.com does not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of eighteen (18). If you have reason to believe a child has provided data to videomarketingqueen.com, please contact us and we will delete that information from our databases. 
> 
>   
>  **CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
>  We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. 
> 
> If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
> 
>   
>  **OPT-OUT POLICY**  
>  If you no longer wish to receive communications from us or if you wish to be removed from our members-only database, Videomarketingqueen.com gives you the following three options:   
>  1) Check the appropriate “Opt Out” link in any applicable email communication or newsletter  
>  2) Send an email to clientsupport@mygoldminevideo.com requesting to be removed from our database  
>  3) Write to us at Video Marketing Queen Inc., 18 S Marengo Ave, Pasadena, CA 91101 requesting to be removed from our database
> 
> **QUESTIONS**  
>  If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us at [support@videomarketingqueen.com](mailto:clientsupport@mygoldminevideo.com).
> 
> [[ Privacy Policy ]](http://www.socialmediatrafficblueprint.com/privacy.html) [[ Terms of Use ]](http://www.socialmediatrafficblueprint.com/tos.html) [[ Purchase Agreement ]](http://www.socialmediatrafficblueprint.com/purchase_agreement.html) [[ Earnings Disclaimer ] ](http://www.socialmediatrafficblueprint.com/earnings.html)
> 
> © 2009 by Video Marketing Queen Inc.
